[{"question":" What are the names of Kim\u0027s and Kanye\u0027s kids?","a1":"North, Saint, Boston, Stormi","a2":" North, Saint, Chicago, Psalm","a3":" South, Saint, Chicago, File","a4":"North, Saint, Chicago, File","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"How many relationships are mentioned in Ariana Grande\u0027s song \"thank u, next\" ?","a1":"4","a2":"5","a3":"3","a4":"15","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"What was the first non-English-language film to win Best Picture at the Oscars?","a1":"100 Dinge","a2":"Parasite","a3":"Amélie","a4":"Der geilste Tag","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"Which of these actresses stared in \"Breakfast at Tiffany\u0027s?\"","a1":"Katherine Hepburn","a2":"Marilyn Monroe","a3":"Joan Fontaine","a4":"Audrey Hepburn","correctAnswer":4},{"question":"Who was declared by Forbes as \"World\u0027s Youngest Billionaire\" at the age of 22 in 2019?","a1":"Billie Eilish","a2":"Taylor Swift","a3":"Kylie Jenner","a4":"Ariana Grande","correctAnswer":3},{"question":"Which TV show follows the lives of Rachel, Monica, Phoebe, Ross, Chandler, and Joey?","a1":"Friends","a2":"The Neighbourhood","a3":"Frenemies","a4":"Blondies","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Who is the most Grammy-awarded artist of ALL TIME?","a1":"Michael Jackson","a2":"2:Stevie Wonder","a3":"Quincy Jones","a4":"Beyoncé","correctAnswer":4},{"question":"Who wore the iconic meat dress in 2010?","a1":"Rihanna","a2":"Lady Gaga","a3":"Kesha","a4":"Nicki Minaj","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"How much approximate revenue did TikTok generate in year 2022?","a1":"1:$3.3 billion","a2":"$ 11.50 billion","a3":"3:$ 9.4 billion","a4":"4:$ 5.3 billion","correctAnswer":3},{"question":"\" I want a church girl that go to church,...\"","a1":"\"...and read her bible\"","a2":"\"...and pray to Jesus\"","a3":"\"...and leave out the door\"","a4":"\"...and discuss Taylor\u0027s polynomials\"","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"*speaking on the phone* \"And they were Roommates!\"","a1":"\"Omg were they?!\"","a2":"\"Omg they were Roommates..\"","a3":"\"You mean Patricia?\"","a4":"\"I thought they were American.\"","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"How many units did the PS5 sell in 2023?","a1":"22.5 million","a2":"20.1 million","a3":"9.8 million","a4":"17.7 million","correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Which Royal was Princess Diana married to?","a1":"Charles II","a2":"Charles III","a3":"Rupaul Charles III","a4":"Prince Harry","correctAnswer":2},{"question":"Which female artist achieved global success as a member of The Fugees before starting a successful solo career?","a1":"Mary J. Blige","a2":"SZA","a3":"Missy Elliott","a4":"Lauryn Hill","correctAnswer":4},{"question":"What was the biggest pop song of 2023?","a1":"SZA - Kill Bill","a2":" Dua Lipa - Dance the Night","a3":"Miley Cyrus - Flowers","a4":" PinkPantheress - Boy\u0027s A Liar","correctAnswer":3},{"question":"","a1":"","a2":"","a3":"","a4":"","correctAnswer":1}]